<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Siva Dhayalan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Siva Dhayalan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Software</title>
      <link>/posts/awesome-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/awesome-software/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of software I have found before but I could never rememeber the name when I am trying to brag about them to someone. So, I am putting it back where I found them.
Windows Tools  https://the-eye.eu/public/MSDN/ https://github.com/Nummer/Destroy-Windows-10-Spying  Interesting  http://mute.fm/  Web Services  http://www.10minutemail.com/ https://privacy.com/ - create virtual credit cards http://gen.lib.rus.ec/ - ebooks http://gen.lib.rus.ec/ - ebooks https://weboas.is/ - new tab http://www.myfridgefood.com/ - food https://opencourser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clever and Useful Finds</title>
      <link>/posts/clever-and-useful-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/clever-and-useful-materials/</guid>
      <description>The following are a non-comprehensive list of articles and links I have come across that are note-worthy
 NES.css: 8-bit style CSS framework - https://bcrikko.github.io/NES.css/ 12 Factor CLI Apps - https://medium.com/@jdxcode/12-factor-cli-apps-dd3c227a0e46 Modern Backend Developer - https://medium.com/tech-tajawal/modern-backend-developer-in-2018-6b3f7b5f8b9
 The Importance of Keeping A Notebook  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Motivated</title>
      <link>/posts/get-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/get-motivated/</guid>
      <description>When you spend half your wake time on the interwebs every single day, you are bound to come across some materials that you find amusing, clever or motivating. That does not mean, I need constant motivation through somebody else&amp;rsquo;s work but some work or compilation do open a different kind world you have never explored or thought of. The following are some of meterials I had clipped some years back on Evernote (sorry, Evernote, you dug your own grave).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Linux for Web Development</title>
      <link>/posts/setting-up-linux-for-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/setting-up-linux-for-dev/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Windows for the last 15 years. I have always used Linux on the side for fun and tinkering but never tried it full time until a couple of years ago. I have been trying various distros for a while now, switching between Ubuntu Unity, Linux Cinamon, Manjaro, until I tried Kubuntu with KDE plasma. The sheer amount of cuztomizations right out of the box and support for HiDPI screen for Lenovo Yoga 2 Pro meant I could stick to this for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>These projects are done in my free time and most of them are as old as 15 years. Work projects are not listed here, but they showcase my skills better than any of these projects do. Contact me if you want to know about my work projects. Thank you.
Simple Sketch - Android Application  I got tired of feature-rich and slow note-taking apps that require whole bunch of permissions to run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>வணக்கம்</title>
      <link>/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%A3%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%A3%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D/</guid>
      <description>நான் சிவா. நான் ஒரு மென்பொருள் கட்டுமான பொறியியலாளர்.
தமிழின் மீது மிகுந்த அன்பும் ஆர்வமும் கொண்டதால், கட்டாயமாக தமிழில் ஒரு பக்கமாவது நானே தட்டச்சு செய்து ஒரு பக்கம் எனது வளையத்தளத்தில் பதிவு செய்ய வேண்டும் என்பது எனது ஆசை. அதனால் அதிகாலை இரண்டு மணிக்கு இதை எனது கையடக்க தொலை பேசியில் எழுதிக்கொண்டிருக்கிறேன்.
அவ்வப்போது தமிழில் ஓரிரு பக்கங்கள் உருவாக்க நினைத்திருக்கிறேன், பார்க்கலாம்.
தமிழன் என்று சொல்லடா, தலை நிமிர்ந்து நில்லடா! ✌</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>Hi there, I am Siva.
I am a Ryerson University graduate, currently working as a Full Stack Web Developer in Toronto. I&amp;rsquo;m also a coffee-lover, environmentalist, minimalist, novice photographer and a self-proclaimed car racer, among other things.
Check out my projects or my photos.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>