<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Siva Dhayalan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Siva Dhayalan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Podcasts</title>
      <link>/posts/recommended-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/recommended-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>As I much as I do like to boast about the sheer amount podcasts listen(ed) to, it is not the intention of this posts. Rather, I find this a good place to share such details about me and document myself. Think of these pages like my facebook wall, minus the likes and comments, plus the added bonus of privacy. This page is something I control and no third party has access to it (except Google analytics, until I configure matamo).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Software</title>
      <link>/posts/awesome-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/awesome-software/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of software I have found before but I could never rememeber the name when I am trying to brag about them to someone. So, I am putting it back where I found them. I am not planning on categorizing the list. I am just going to append to the list as I come across interesting projects on Hacker News and other sources. Consider this my TODO list, so this is neither exhaustive nor meant to be a guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Life Advice</title>
      <link>/posts/random-life-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/random-life-advice/</guid>
      <description>I found the following &amp;lsquo;article&amp;rsquo; somewhere in the interwebs and had saved it some years ago. Since I was cleaning up my evernote, I wanted to keep this somewhere I can point people to or read it sometimes. This is neither a exhaustive guide to life nor is it a definitive way to live life but I am sure it might inspire some people to try different things as it did for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>These projects are done in my free time and some of them are as old as 15 years. Only some work projects and freelance projects are listed here. Please contact me for more details.
Computek College  Developled this WP site within a month since the client had to move to a new site by graduation. This site perfectly captures the clients needs. They wanted a simple and minimalistic site with only the essential information categorized into different pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>வணக்கம்</title>
      <link>/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%A3%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/%E0%AE%B5%E0%AE%A3%E0%AE%95%E0%AF%8D%E0%AE%95%E0%AE%AE%E0%AF%8D/</guid>
      <description>நான் சிவா. நான் ஒரு மென்பொருள் கட்டுமான பொறியியலாளர்.
தமிழின் மீது மிகுந்த அன்பும் ஆர்வமும் கொண்டதால், கட்டாயமாக தமிழில் ஒரு பக்கமாவது நானே தட்டச்சு செய்து எனது வளையத்தளத்தில் பதிவு செய்ய வேண்டும் என்பது எனது ஆசை. அதனால் அதிகாலை இரண்டு மணிக்கு இதை எனது கையடக்க தொலை பேசியில் எழுதிக்கொண்டிருக்கிறேன்.
அவ்வப்போது தமிழில் ஓரிரு பக்கங்கள் உருவாக்க நினைத்திருக்கிறேன், பார்க்கலாம்.
✌</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/</guid>
      <description>Hi. I am Siva.
I am a CompSci graduate from Ryerson University, currently working as a Full Stack Web Developer in Toronto. I&amp;rsquo;m also a novice photographer, environmentalist/minimalist, among other things.
I also freelance depending on type of project. Send me an email to get a quote.
Check out my projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>