<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Siva Dhayalan</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Siva Dhayalan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful CLI commands</title>
      <link>/posts/useful-cli-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/useful-cli-commands/</guid>
      <description>These are just documentation for me because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to remember them. It is not a guide for anything.
 awk
awk &#39;/regex/&#39; awk &#39;!/regex/&#39; awk &#39;BEGIN{a=5; b=2.5; print a+b}&#39; awk &#39;{sub(/:/, &amp;quot;-&amp;quot;)} 1&#39; // subtitution awk &#39;{gsub(/:/, &amp;quot;-&amp;quot;)} 1&#39;  List network devices
Win: arp -a  Make VS Code remember Github credentials; Easier if you are working with multiple accounts for work and personal.
git config credential.helper store  Install Node</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommended Podcasts</title>
      <link>/posts/recommended-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/recommended-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>As I much as I do like to boast about the sheer amount podcasts listen(ed) to, it is not the intention of this posts. Rather, I find this a good place to share such details about me and document myself. Think of these pages like my facebook wall, minus the likes and comments, plus the added bonus of privacy. This page is something I control and no third party has access to it (except Google analytics, until I configure matamo).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Software/Websites</title>
      <link>/posts/awesome-software/websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/awesome-software/websites/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of software I have found before but I could never rememeber the name when I am trying to brag about them to someone. So, I am putting it back where I found them. I am not planning on categorizing the list. I am just going to append to the list as I come across interesting projects on Hacker News and other sources. Consider this my TODO list, so this is neither exhaustive nor meant to be a guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misc Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>/posts/misc-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misc-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description> Virtual Box issue on Windows 10 If you are not able to get Vitual Box in Windows, try running the following (as admin)
dism.exe /Online /Disable-Feature:Microsoft-Hyper-V bcdedit /set hypervisorlaunchtype off  Also make sure to remove the following from Windows Program and Features: - Hyper-V
- Virtualizing Platform </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Life Advice</title>
      <link>/posts/random-life-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/random-life-advice/</guid>
      <description>I found the following &amp;lsquo;article&amp;rsquo; somewhere in the interwebs and had saved it some years ago. Since I was cleaning up my evernote, I wanted to keep this somewhere I can point people to or read it sometimes. This is neither a exhaustive guide to life nor is it a definitive way to live life but I am sure it might inspire some people to try different things as it did for me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>